(Raj:)-She won't notice they're missing?
-She doesn't know she takes them.
(Leonard:)No, that's okay. It was something else
keeping me up last night.
(Leonard:)And again this morning.
(Leonard:)And I didn't mind.
(Leonard:)I was up last night.
I was up this morning. I didn't mind.
(Leonard:)Those are your clues.
(Raj:)Ooh, ooh, did the pigeon
on your windowsill have more babies?
(Raj:)-No.
-Were you making another Lego movie?
-Because let me tell you:
(Howard:)It's not enough to make the Legos move.
They also have to capture your heart.
(Leonard:)Okay, I'll give you one more clue.
(Leonard:)It involved another person.
(Raj:)Did you get a Japanese love pillow?
(Howard:)How is a Japanese love pillow
another person?
(Raj:)It is if you love her
and give her a name.